<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on Vector.js</title>
    <link>https://vectorjs.org/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on Vector.js</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://vectorjs.org/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Derek</title>
      <link>https://vectorjs.org/team/derek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vectorjs.org/team/derek/</guid>
      <description>I am an undergraduate senior working on a computer science bachelor’s degree. Outside of school, I’m passionate about music, running, and the outdoors. My experience being both a student and teaching assistant in programming has made me appreciate the value in tools that are powerful and still easy to learn. My motivation for this project has been to be a part of creating such a tool that helps others to learn and enjoy writing code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh</title>
      <link>https://vectorjs.org/team/josh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vectorjs.org/team/josh/</guid>
      <description>I am 23 years old and graduating this semester with a degree in Computer Science. Some of my favorite hobbies are video games, puzzles, and running. My academic interests outside of computing include sociology, art, and world religion. My interest in this project comes from creating geographic weather interactives, and seeing how challening it was to use existing tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kurt</title>
      <link>https://vectorjs.org/team/kurt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vectorjs.org/team/kurt/</guid>
      <description>I am a senior graduating this december with a computer science degree. In addition to this project I also built a website about math that utilizes this library to create interactive math visuals. I am currently looking for a job where I can continue to learn, meet new people, and develop good software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zach</title>
      <link>https://vectorjs.org/team/zach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vectorjs.org/team/zach/</guid>
      <description>I am a senior in the combined BS/MS computer science program and will graduate in Spring 2021. I am currently interested in research opportunities and hope to continue my education after graduating by participating in a PhD program. I am especially interested in data visualization and am a part of the Visualization Design Lab here at Utah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
